// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Mind mapping is a tool used to visually organize information that helps us to analyze, synthesize, recall and __________ new ideas.",
    answer: "c. evaluate",
    options: [
      "a. draw",
      "b. estimate",
      "c. evaluate",
      "d. generate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which technique in making a movie is used to generate the illusion of movement from many still images?",
    answer: "a. animation",
    options: [
      "a. animation",
      "b. designing",
      "c. video filming",
      "d. photography"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "This is a short Filipino poem that consists of 4 lines with 7-7-7-7 syllabic verse.",
    answer: "c. tanaga",
    options: [
      "a. awit",
      "b. haiku",
      "c. tanaga",
      "d. sonnet"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Blog is the short term for __________.",
    answer: "b. web blog",
    options: [
      "a. net blog",
      "b. web blog",
      "c. word blog",
      "d. internet blog"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The following media forms are integrated in multimedia EXCEPT _________.",
    answer: "d. animation",
    options: [
      "a. text",
      "b. video",
      "c. computer",
      "d. animation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "PowerPoint application is used to _________.",
    answer: "b. create slideshow presentations",
    options: [
      "a. design animations",
      "b. create slideshow presentations",
      "c. process and store digital presentations",
      "d. generate ideas from people thru mapping"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which wireless handheld device is used to make and receive calls and send text messages?",
    answer: "b. cellphone",
    options: [
      "a. laptop",
      "b. cellphone",
      "c. desktop",
      "d. camera"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "This electronic device is used for storing and processing data.",
    answer: "c. computer",
    options: [
      "a. printer",
      "b. android",
      "c. computer",
      "d. mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A tag cloud is also known as _________.",
    answer: "c. word cloud",
    options: [
      "a. web cloud",
      "b. text cloud",
      "c. word cloud",
      "d. digital cloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which software package is designed to create electronic presentations consisting of a series of separate pages?",
    answer: "a. PowerPoint",
    options: [
      "a. PowerPoint",
      "b. Mobile text tula",
      "c. Microsoft Excel",
      "d. Digital photography"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "This refers to an electronic medium for recording, copying, playing back, broadcasting, and displaying moving visual media.",
    answer: "b. video",
    options: [
      "a. audio",
      "b. video",
      "c. computer",
      "d. animation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following statements is TRUE?",
    answer: "d. Integration of multimedia in studying literature enhances learner’s ICT skills.",
    options: [
      "a. Multimedia use in learning is expensive.",
      "b. Multimedia solely uses graphics and animation.",
      "c. Learners are encouraged to use only one multimedia format.",
      "d. Integration of multimedia in studying literature enhances learner’s ICT skills."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The following are multimedia formats except __________.",
    answer: "c. paint",
    options: [
      "a. blog",
      "b. video",
      "c. paint",
      "d. tag cloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "It is used to describe any sound in terms of receiving, transmitting or reproducing its specific frequency.",
    answer: "a. audio",
    options: [
      "a. audio",
      "b. noise",
      "c. video",
      "d. frequency"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "If a learner desires to create informational discussion on the web about people’s travel, interests, and experiences, he/she can create a _________.",
    answer: "a. blog",
    options: [
      "a. blog",
      "b. essay",
      "c. tag cloud",
      "d. mobile text tula"
    ]
  },
];
